This is the section of pregnant women,
who are here for safe delivery.
Many of them have been booked for operations because of complications.
They are here looking in faith to our Lord and Saviour Jesus Christ to be free
so that they can deliver their babies safely without any complications,
without any surgical operations.
BABY BORN As PASTOR PRAYS!!!
Here is one of those have come today for safe delivery,
BABY BORN AS PASTOR PRAYS!!!
The resurrection power of our Lord and Saviour Jesus Christ is working in the midst of the people.
I can see what is happening to this pregnant woman
See what she passed out as the man of God stretched forth his hand towards her,
praying for her in the name of Jesus Christ.
Receive deliverance!
Be free! Out!
Come out!
Out, Ezekiel!
BABY BORN AS PASTOR PRAYS!!!
What you have just watched is the miraculous birth of baby Ezekiel.
Mrs. Geneva Amam had come to the SCOAN with complications in her pregnancy.
The doctors had diagnosed a tight cervix
for which they had booked her for an operation.
Prophet T.B. Joshua prayed for Geneva in the prayer line
and immediately, her water broke and she went into labour.
Some moments later, Prophet T.B. Joshua went to her at the labour room
and spoke a word of prophecy,
identifying both the name and the gender of the child,
saying, "Ezekiel, come out!"
Instantly, baby Ezekiel was delivered.
Testimony time
Emmanuel!
(God With Us - Matthew 1:23)
My name is Geneva Amam, I am from Imo state.
I am 30 years old.
The problem that brought me to The SCOAN last Sunday
was that of a tight cervix for which I was booked for an operation
and also that of high blood pressure.
When all these things were happening, I was rejected by 2 to 3 hospitals.
They said the baby was too big and they could not handle the baby.
The one that accepted later said that because of the high blood pressure,
they would not be able to operate on me.
The cervix was tight, there was no way the baby could come out
and my blood pressure was too high for them to operate on me.
So my husband now took me down to The SCOAN
where I was arranged at the emergency section
and the man of God prayed for me.
Immediately he touched my foot with his foot, the water that
was holding the baby and making the cervix tight burst
and poured out instantly and my body became cool and calm.
After some time, labour started, yet the baby could not come out.
The man of God came and prayed for me and said, "Ezekiel, come out!"
Instantly - where the power came from, I can't imagine -
the baby just came out; all I heard was the cry of a baby and he's a baby boy.
I was shocked, I was surprised. I said, "How?
How did the man of God know that I was carrying a baby boy?"
The whole thing - I was like crying, but I give God the glory
because the baby is alive and I myself, I'm alive, strong and healthy.
That is why we are here today to glorify the name of God, to bless His name
because what man cannot do, God did through the able hand of
His anointed servant, Prophet T.B. Joshua.
And here, you can see me carrying Ezekiel.
I thank God for that; I give God all the glory.
I am Mr. Patrick Amam.
The woman next to me is my wife, Mrs Geneva Amam.
The baby's name is Ezekiel Amam. He was delivered in last Sunday's service.
We had the problem of my wife being unable to deliver her baby safely in the hospital.
Before 4 am that Sunday morning, I called the hospital -
she told me that she had not delivered, and worse, still that she had a tight cervix.
I ran down to the hospital as early as 4 am.
I noticed that my wife had even become weak and had developed high blood pressure.
I knew that we needed God's intervention.
We could not trust the medical operation they had given us as an option for the delivery.
I told my wife, "All you need is God's intervention".
I took her away. The hospital objected.
I said, "Keep our load. If God intervenes, I can return her to you."
Then they allowed us to go.
We came here directly - my wife and I to the emergency line of The SCOAN.
We had the luck that the man of God came and prayed for her.
The first time the man of God prayed for her, the cervix opened,
the water gushed out and my wife felt cool in her system.
I had peace; I was happy.
The man of God came the second time and mentioned the sex of the baby
while the baby was still in the womb - 'Ezekiel' three times.
He said, "Ezekiel, come out!" and the boy rushed out immediately and cried.
There was jubilation everywhere in the church.
We give God the glory.
I thank God for this mercy and favour for my family.
We believe you have been inspired by the clip you have just watched.
Click here to subscribe, to witness more of God's power at work in our generation today
and stay up-to-date for the latest prophecies, deliverances,
sermons and testimonies from The SCOAN.
Emmanuel TV - Changing lives, Changing nations and Changing the world.
RV: Mel Flowers 24/03/2019